[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many young skunks can be born in one litter?", "correct_answer": "1-7", "incorrect_answers": ["1-10", "1-5", "1-4"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which youthful musician(s) is/are associated with the 1980s albums Killing Joke and Whats THIS for...!?", "correct_answer": "Martin Youth Glover", "incorrect_answers": ["Paul Young", "Musical Youth", "Neil Young"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these animals makes the loudest noise?", "correct_answer": "The humpback whale", "incorrect_answers": ["The Andean condor", "The whale shark", "The howling monkey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All telephones in the USA were shut down on August 2, 1922. Why?", "correct_answer": "It was the day when Alexander Graham Bell died.", "incorrect_answers": ["The International Brotherhod of Communications Workers went on strike.", "The electrical workers in New York, Chicago, and Washington went on strike.", "It was the day  for the Orson Welles  War of the Worlds radio telecast."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The American Philatelic Society is the U.S. organization of the fans of one of the worlds most popular hobbies. Which is it?", "correct_answer": "Stamp collecting", "incorrect_answers": ["Coin collecting", "Knitting", "Matchbox collecting"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The names of Popeyes four nephews are Pipeye, Peepeye, Pupeye, and Poopeye.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chinese Crested dogs are very suspicious of strangers and can make very good watchdogs.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Topic: Fast Foods: This restaurant carries Chicken Tenders, Burger Shots and the Double Croissanwich. Ask the right question.", "correct_answer": "What is Burger King?", "incorrect_answers": ["What is Jack in the Box?", "What is Wendys?", "What is Arbys?"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Most fairy tale characters have this color hair.", "correct_answer": "Blonde", "incorrect_answers": ["Dark", "Green", "Red"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Animal liver is very rich in this health-beneficial mineral, as well as in vitamin A.", "correct_answer": "Iron", "incorrect_answers": ["Magnesium", "Calcium", "Potassium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are billions of these microscopic creatures in your bed and they feed on this.", "correct_answer": "Dead skin cells", "incorrect_answers": ["Wood", "Cotton fibres", "Sweat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In contract bridge, yarborough is a term referring to what type of hand?", "correct_answer": "Containing no points at all", "incorrect_answers": ["Containing 4 jacks", "Containing only one color", "Containing 4 queens and 4 kings"]}]